Lesson 16 Bob brings the cookies to the village market.
Bob brings Carol the cookies.
He tells Carol that baking the cookies was easy because he had lots of help.
Bob, how did the baking go?
Slow at first, but we're getting the hang of it.
Once you learn the ropes, it becomes second nature.
To tell you the truth, I thought that baking 2,000 cookies would be a pain in the neck,
but we managed to round up some helpers, and it was a piece of cake.
Well, thanks for coming in person with the cookies.
No problem. When will you need more?
It depends on how many we sell today.
How many do you think you'll sell?
Maybe 500, maybe 2,000.
Your guess is as good as mine.
In any case, I'll keep you posted.
Okay, just give me a ring as soon as you know.